moneyqanda.com 2017-11-19

# Money Q&A's Privacy Policy to Protect Your Information and Privacy

**Your Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Money Q&A has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
When visiting Money Q&A, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to third party Websites**  
We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**  
The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Money Q&A then you may contact us at hank@moneyqanda.com

**Compensation Disclosure**

**I am paid to review websites, eBooks, blogs, and products.**  I am paid with money, free stuff, and sometimes both. If you see a review on this site, please assume that it is a paid review. At the same time, please do rest assured that payment never sways my opinion.

This Compensation Disclosure has been provided for your protection and to fully disclose any relationship between this sites product or service recommendations and the owners of those product or services. The owner of this website is required by the FTC to inform you that a relationship exists between Money Q&A and some of the products or services it reviews, recommends or promotes.

Money Q&A makes use of affiliate relationships with merchants for monetization. This means when you click on links to various merchants on this site and make a purchase, this can result in a commission that is credited to this site.

The opinions expressed here are those of myself as an individual and are not necessarily the opinions of nor reflect the views of any merchants I am affiliated with. I have chosen to only recommend products and services on Money Q&A that I use or have thoroughly researched. I earn a full-time living as an affiliate marketer, so it is essential that I maintain my credibility.

The Money Q&A traffic is increasing monthly. A lot of people who come here for advice, help, and support. I take my responsibility as an affiliate and subject matter expert very seriously.
